We will start this exercise with the 3 to 1 method.
Find a comfortable position,
close your eyes, take a deep breath and while exhaling mentally
repeat and visualize the number three three times.
To help you learn to relax physically at level 3, I'm going
to direct your attention to different parts of your body.
Relax your scalp, relax your forehead, relax your eyes and the
tissue you surrounding your eyes.
Relax your face.
Relax your throat, externally and internally.
Relax your shoulders, arms and hands.
Relax your chest externally and internally Relax your abdominal
area externally and internally
Relax your thighs.
Relax your knees.
Relax your calves.
Relax your feet.
Recall the wonderful feeling of deep physical relaxation.
You are now at a deeper healthier level of mind deeper than
before.
This is your physical relaxation level 3. 3 Whenever you
mentally repeat and visualize the number 3, your body will relax
as completely as you are now and more so every time you
practice.
To enter mental relaxation level 2, take a deep breath and while
exhaling mentally repeat Repeat and visualize the number 2 three
times.
Level 2 is for mental relaxation, where noises will not distract
you, instead, noises will help you to relax mentally more and
more. more.
To improve mental relaxation at level 2, practice visualizing
tranquil and passive scenes.
Take another deep breath and while exhaling, mentally repeat and
visualize number 1 3 times.
you are now at level one a deeper healthier level of mind
where you can function from your center
to help you enter a deeper healthier level of mind I'm going
to count from ten to one on each descending number you will
feel yourself going deeper and you will enter a deeper
healthier level of mind ten nine feel going deeper eight seven
six deeper and deeper 5 4 3 deeper and deeper 2 1
you are now at a deeper healthier level of mind deeper than
before it is a wonderful feeling to be deeply relaxed a A
very healthy state of being.
Effective sensory projection statements for success.
I will be speaking in your place.
I am now able to attune my intelligence by developing my sensing
faculties and to experience myself myself as any point or place,
level or depth, so as to become aware of any actions taking
place.
I am able to function in non -locality regarding time and space.
I am aware that intelligence exists at all levels and depths in
the universe and therefore I can attune to all information.
I am now able to use my sensing faculties and to experience
myself as any matter kingdom mineral plant animal and human if
this is what I desire to do I am now able to
detect abnormalities whenever such abnormalities exist within
any kingdom,
any level,
any depth.
I am now able to apply corrective measures and to bring back
to normalcy any abnormality found within any kingdom,
any level, and any depth.
Energy is available at any level to be acted upon to create
through the subjective and objective dimensions.
In a moment, I'm going to count slowly from 10 to 1
so that you can attune yourself to universal source energy and
your life's purpose.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. One, open
yourself to thoughts, feelings, sounds,
sights, or sensations that give you a sense of your purpose in
life.
Ask universal source energy.
what is your vision for my purpose in life continue to deepen
and experience what comes to you what does it look like what
does it feel like and sound like pay close attention to symbols
or other types of representations when something comes to you
write it down
remember to write down anything that comes to mind even though
you feel you're making it up
Write down images, thoughts, colors, ideas that surface for each
question.
Then simply take a deep breath and return to your center.
once again the question to universal source energy is what is
your vision for my purpose in life
Thank you.
next ask universal source energy what is it that I have to
become in order for For this purpose to manifest, write down
anything that comes to mind.
Thank you.
now ask universal source energy what must I let go of or
release in order to fulfill my purpose what must I let go
of or release in order to fulfill my purpose
write down anything that comes to mind
Thank you.
now ask universal source energy what must I embrace what must I
embrace write Write down anything that comes to mind.
Thank you.
Thank you. Finally, you can ask Source Energy,
Is there anything else I need to know?
Open yourself up to what comes to mind and write down anything.
Thank you.
Imagine yourself with the qualities you need in order to fulfill
your life's purpose by being joyous and loving.
while in a deep meditative state
begin to experience your life's purpose from deep within
what you have to know
what you have to become
what you have to embody and change
imagine what you are meant to do in order to express that
joy and love
Remember this feeling.
Every time you function at these levels of the mind and at
these points of reference, you will receive beneficial effects
physically and mentally.
You may use these levels of the mind and these points of
reference to help yourself, to help your loved ones, and to help
any human being who needs help, physically and mentally.
You will always use these levels of the mind and these points
of reference in a constructive, creative manner, for all that is
good, honest, pure, clean, and positive, and this is so.
You will continue to strive to take part in constructive and
creative activities to make this a better world to live in, so
that when you move on, you shall have left behind a better
world for those who follow.
You will consider the whole of humanity, depending on their
ages, as fathers or mothers, brothers or sisters, sons or
daughters.
You are a superior human being. You have greater understanding,
compassion, and patience with others.
in a moment I'm going to count from 1 to 5 and
cause a sound with my fingers
at that moment you will open your eyes be wide awake feeling
fine and in perfect health
feeling better than before
feeling the way you feel when you have slept the right amount
of revitalizing, refreshing
relaxing relaxing, healthy sleep.
One, two, coming out slowly now.
Three, at the count of five, you will open your eyes, be
wide awake, feeling fine and in perfect health,
feeling better than before.
Four, five, eyes open, wide awake, feeling fine and in perfect
health, feeling better than before.
To guarantee success with your Silva techniques, we recommend
that you take the Silva seminars live. For more information over
course schedules and locations, log on to silvamethod .com or
call 1 -800 -545 -6463 within the continental United States or
956 -722 -6391.
Thank you.